UNITE Local 169 Files 6000/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 169 Files
1990-2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Local 169
6000/016
16.5 cubic feet
16.5 linear ft.
Records.
6766545
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 24, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/016 MB: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Memorabilia Banners 6000/016 P: UNITE Local 169 Amalgamated Northeast Regional Joint Board Photographs
Collective bargaining -- Clothing industry -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- New York (State); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Local 169 (New York, N.Y.); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 169 (New York, N.Y.); UNITE HERE (Organization)
6766545
- 2nd Avenue Green Grocers (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 8th Ave. Gourmet & Grocery (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alpine 45 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 53 Gourmet Affidavits (Duplicates) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 53 Gourmet - NLRB Election (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 53 Gourmet Deli Cards (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 53 Gourmet Deli (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 53 Gourmet Deli (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 53 Gourmet - Ownership (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 53 Gourmet (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Canova, Inc. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 54 Broadway Caf (54 Grocery Inc.) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 54 Broadway Caf (54 Grocery Inc.) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 75 Park Farm (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 86 St. Grocers (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 99 John's Market Place (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 99 John's Market Place ILA (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 103 Grocery and Vegetable Fruit (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 345 Produce Inc. (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ernesto Dominguez (Abbigail) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Abbigail (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Abbigail leaflets & Letters (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Abbigail, East Natural, SoHo Natural, Corporate Info (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Abbigail Company Leaflets (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Abbigail - Retail, Wholesale Warehouse and Production Employees (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Abbigail / Regale Deli ULP (Box 1, Folder 26)
- ULP Abbigail and W (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Adinah's Farm (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Adinah's Farm (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Alpine 7 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Alpine Gourmet 968 6th Ave. (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Alpine Gourmet Deli (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Alpine Gourmet (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Alpine Gourmet Deli (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Amish (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Oahu Deli (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Azure (CSJ & Co. Inc.) 830 3rd Ave (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Back Stage Eatery (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bee America Deli (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Bee America Deli (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Big Banana (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Broadway Fancy Foods (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Bo & Kenny Enterprises (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Bo & Kenny Enterprises Inc. (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Bocca Della Nona Corp. 135 W. 50th (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Caf 39 Gourmet Deli (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Caf 39 Gourmet Deli (Box 1, Folder 47)
- C and N (Box 1, Folder 48)
- C and N Fruit and Vegetable 229 Ave B (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Caf 49 Inc. (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Caf 49 Interviews (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Caf 49 Inc. (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Caf 49, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  Scope and Contents
  January 1-20
- Central Deli, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  February 21
- Central Caf Deli (Pronto Caf Deli) 16 Vanderbilt Ave (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Central Deli Caf (Deli Closs Enterprises Inc.) (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Central Caf Deli (Pronto Central Deli) 16 Vanderbilt Ave (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Champs (71 Broadway) (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Canova Inc. (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Champs (71 Broadway) (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Checkerboard - 519 Madison Ave (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Checkerboard Gourmet Inc. (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Chefs Kitchen (Checkerboard) Ownership (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Cielo Gourmet (Box 1, Folder 64)
- D&D Market (Spring Grocery Inc.) (Box 1, Folder 65)
- D&D Market (Spring Grocery Inc.) (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Deli on Madison (420 Gourmet Corp.) (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Deli on Madison 420 Gourmet Corp. (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Deli and Grocery (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Deli and Grocery (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Duna's (Box 1, Folder 71)
- East Natural (Box 1, Folder 71)
- East Natural - Community Complaints (Box 1, Folder 72)
- East Natural Food Market (Box 1, Folder 73)
- East Natural, et al (Box 1, Folder 74)
- East Natural et al Back Wage Lawsuit (1) (Box 1, Folder 75)
- East Natural et al Back Wage Lawsuit (2) (Box 1, Folder 76)
- East Natural et al Back Wage Lawsuit (3) (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Settlement of East Natural et al consolidated ULP (Box 2, Folder 1)
- East Natural - List of Workers (Box 2, Folder 2)
- East Natural Firings - Velez, F; Saquedra, G; Solano, A, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  March 29
- East Natural NJRB Petition (Box 2, Folder 4)
- East Natural ULP Pastor Baltazar (Box 2, Folder 5)
- East Natural NLRB - Petition (Box 2, Folder 6)
- East Natural VLP 30 Day Recognition Picketing (Box 2, Folder 7)
- East Village Farmers Market (Box 2, Folder 8)
- East Village Market (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Eden Farm (Box 2, Folder 10)
- F and R Kim Mart (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fine & Shapiro Restaurant Delicatessen Inc. 5 World Trade Center (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Fine & Shapiro 5 World Trade Center (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Food Dynasty 50 - 18 Skillman Ave Queens, NY 11377 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Four J Grocery (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Four J Grocery (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Fraiche (6 E. 48th St.) (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Fraiche (213 Park Ave. Gourmet) (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Fruit City (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Fruit & Vegetables (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Fruit & Vegetable (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fuji (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Fuji Apple Fruit + Vegetable (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Galaxy - 3rd Ave. & 10th St. (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Garden Fruit & Vegetable 420 E. 14th St. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Grace Gourmet Deli (198 Broadway Gourmet Corp.) (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Grace Gourmet Deli (198 Broadway Gourmet Corp.) (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Graceland (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Grand Central Deli - Employee List, etc. (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Grand Central Place (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Green Emporium (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Green Emporium (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Green Emporium (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Green Farm (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Green Farm (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Goldiggers Corp. (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Goldigger Corp. (Box 2, Folder 36)
- H & S Fruit & Vegetables (Box 2, Folder 37)
- H + S Fruit and Vegetables Inc. (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Hanna's (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Hannae's Produce (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Healthy Pleasures (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Hee I (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Hee II (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Hee Deli and Grocery (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Highpoint Gourmet Corp (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Indian American Grocery (Box 2, Folder 46)
- J & H Farms (Together Market) 245 Park Ave S. (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Jade Garden Gourmet (Five J Food Corp.) 835, 3rd Ave (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Jin Market (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Jin Market - Article 20 AFL-CIO (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Jin Market - Back Wages (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Jin Market Back Wages (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Community Support - Jin Market (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Jin Market - Hudson Market NLRB Election Petition (Box 2, Folder 54)
- NLRB Election Petition Jin Market (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Jin Market - Contract (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Jin Market ILA Cards (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Jin Market - ULP 2-CA-3345-1 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Jin Market Hudson Market ULP's (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Jin Market Affidavits Duplicates (Box 2, Folder 60)
- John Jay College (Box 2, Folder 61)
- JSK (Box 2, Folder 62)
- JSK - NLRB (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Lee & Elle (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Liberty Gourmet Deli (32 Broadway Deli Food) (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Liberty Gourmet Deli (32 Broadway Deli Food) (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Longwood Gourmet Inc. (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Longwood Gourmet Inc. (Box 2, Folder 68)
- K + S Fruit and Vegetables (Box 2, Folder 69)
- KAC Market (Box 2, Folder 70)
- KC Market (Box 2, Folder 71)
- KCS - 123 Lexington Ave. Interview Sheets Duplicates (Box 2, Folder 72)
- KCS - 123 Lexington Ave. Interview (Box 2, Folder 73)
- KCS - ULP (Box 2, Folder 74)
- KSC - Misc. Sample Contracts Reco. Etc. (Box 2, Folder 75)
- KSC Food Market 1263 Lexington Ave - Ownership (Box 2, Folder 76)
- KSC Food Market - NLRB Petition (Box 2, Folder 77)
- KSC - ULP's (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Lee's Gourmet - Affidavits (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Lime Tree (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Lucky Deli Cards (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Lucky Deli 138 5th Ave (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Lucky Deli - Affidavits Duplicates (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Lucky Farm Market (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Lucky Farm (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Lucky Farm / Bear Farm, Inc. Recognition (Box 3, Folder 4)
- M & N Deli Salad Bar (54 Broadway Caf) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- M & N Deli Salad Bar (54 Broadway Caf) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- M&N Deli Salad Bar (54 Broadway Caf) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- M&Y Gourmet Groceries (Lucky Market) 138 5th Ave. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- M&Y Gourmet Groceries (Lucky Market) 138 5th Ave (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Metro Deli (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Metro Deli (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Metro Deli - Reco (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Metro Deli - Neg. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Metro Deli - Neg. - Wage Issues (Box 3, Folder 14)
- MIK Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 15)
- MIK Enterprises (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Modern Gourmet, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  March 10
- Modern Gourmet (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Modern Gourmet (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Modern Gourmet Inc. (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Modern Gourmet (Box 3, Folder 21)
- New Blue Flowers Caf (5 E. 47th St.) (Box 3, Folder 22)
- New Blue Flowers Caf (5 E. 47th St.) (Box 3, Folder 23)
- New Star Caf (Box 3, Folder 24)
- New Star Caf Contract (Box 3, Folder 25)
- New Star - Cards (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Old Bardo's Farm (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Olympic Deli & Grocery 217 1st Ave (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Olympic Deli SLRB (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Olympic Deli NLRB Petition (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Olympic Deli NYS Employment Relations Board (Box 3, Folder 31)
- PAKS (Box 3, Folder 32)
- PAKS (Metro) 325 Madison Ave. (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Park Ave. Gourmet (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Produce Inc. 345 1st Ave. (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Piece & Total (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Regale (Formerly Abbigail) (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Reliable Food Market (Reliable Produce Inc.) (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Reliable Food Market (Reliable Produce Inc.) (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Rosa Mexicano (Box 3, Folder 40)
- SKB Deli Inc. ( Narinder Deli) (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Smilers - 544 5th Ave. Interview Sheets (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Smiler's Deli 554 5th Ave. Organizing Info (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Smiler's 544 5th Ave. Interview Sheets (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Smiler's (719 7th Ave.) (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Smiler's (726 8th Ave.) (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Smiley's Delicatessen (532 Madison Ave. Gourmet Foods, Inc.) (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Smiley's Delicatessen (532 Madison Ave. Gourmet Foods Inc.) (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Spring Grocery 67 Spring St. (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Spring Grocery 67 Spring St. (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Times Deli (158 w. 44th St.) (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Soho Company Leaflets (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Soho - Retail Wholesale Warehouse & Production Employees Int. Union (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Soho Natural - ULP's Re: RWWPEU (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Soho Natural - Farid Assel (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Jerry Tolentino (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Police Reports (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Soho Lawsuit (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Soho Natural (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Sok's Grocery (Box 3, Folder 59)
- South Shore (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Spring (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Stuyvesant (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Stuyvesant Farm Market (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Sun Fruit + Vegetables Corp. (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Sun Market (Box 3, Folder 65)
- \ Deli 321 5th Ave. (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Sunny and Annie (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Theresa and Joseph (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Tiffany 1145 Brighton Beach Avenue Brooklyn, NY 11224 (718) (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Times Deli Affidavits Duplicates (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Times Deli (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Together Market (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Top 313 1st Ave. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Top (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Two Brothers Inc. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Two Brothers Grocery (Box 4, Folder 7)
- University Place Gourmet (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Valentino (Box 4, Folder 9)
- WA Fruit and Vegetable Market (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Whitehall Deli Corp. 27 Whitehall St. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Y + H Market (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Young Farmers Market (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Young Farmers Market (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Young's Natural Market Inc. 432 Park Ave. S. (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Green Grocery Information (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Green Grocers Campaign (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Misc. Newspaper Clipping (Box 4, Folder 17)
- UNITE Files (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ehab Elsaadawy (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Documents & Notes From Hearing (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Consolidated ULP (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Wageh Hanna - IRS (Box 4, Folder 22)
- New School Students (Box 4, Folder 23)
- ILA - Documents (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Wagel Hanna Affidavit (Box 4, Folder 25)
- List of Workers: Abbigail, East Natural, Soho Natural (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Translator Affidavits For AG (Box 4, Folder 27)
- L.E.S. (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Special Events Permits (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Fair Wage (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Green Grocer Special Event (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Green Grocer Brighton Beach Listing (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Wages - Adinah's, Fuji's (Box 4, Folder 33)
- KGG (Box 4, Folder 34)
- L.E.S. (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Korean Green Grocers (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Recognition Agreement (Box 5, Folder 1)
- L.E.S. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Jeffrey Eichler (Affidavit) (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Official Papers (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Criminal Court of the City of New York (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Local 169 I.D.'s (Box 5, Folder 6)
- L.E.S. Petitions (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Green grocery End-sweatshop Campaign (Box 5, Folder 8)
- East Village Supermarket Deli (Box 5, Folder 9)
- La Associacion Mexico Americana de Trabajadores (Box 5, Folder 10)
- East Natural etc. Leaflets (Box 5, Folder 11)
- East Natural, Abbigail, Soho (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Brighton Beach Lists, Korean Assoc., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  August 31
- Statistics - Abbigail, East Natural, Soho (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Lower East Side Green Groceries (1) (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Lower East Side Green Groceries (2) (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Lower East Side Green Groceries (3) (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Youth Congress of the 2nd Council Districts, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  August 18
- Mexican-American Workers Activities (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Green Grocers Literature Packets (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Boycotts (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Leaflets - Greengrocers Campaign (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Literature - Press Releases etc. (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Boycott News (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Boycott News (Box 5, Folder 25)
- New Articles (Box 5, Folder 26)
- New Articles (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Boycotts (Box 6, Folder 1)
- City Council Hearing on Greengrocery Resolution, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  February 16
- Community Involvement CLC (Box 6, Folder 3)
- U.S. DOL - Wages & Hours (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Freed/Lopez Meeting (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Greengrocers Misc. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Storeowners Letter (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Meeting with Owners, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  May 5
- Retirees (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Spitzer Report (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Press Conf. Spitzer (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Spitzer - Stores Under Investigion (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Spitzer - Stores Under Investigation (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Staff meeting & Assignments (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Student Surveys - Green grocers (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Updated Survey, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  May 23
- Green Grocery Workers (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Youth Congress (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Campaign (Fall), 2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Plans, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Campaign (Fall)
- Targeting Info, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Targets - Final, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Staff Assignments (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Shop Leadership, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- March 28 Demo, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Boycott, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Boycott Lines, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Student Support, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Student Support - Universities NYC, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- CLC Letter, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  April 3
- Literature - Letters (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Press Demo, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  December 6
- Email - Roy Hong (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Task Force (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Employer Assoc. Const. (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Boycott Demos Calendar (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Labels (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Notes (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Forms (Box 6, Folder 37)
  Back Wage Law Clinic
- NELP - Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 38)
- NELP - Email List (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Forham University (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Back Wages - Lit. Big Store Campaign (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Back Wages - Misc. (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Back Wages - Press (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Korean Greengroceries Local 169 - ILA 2001 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Hearing (Box 6, Folder 45)
  AFL-CIO Article 21
- Mediation (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Mediation (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Notes & Documents (Box 6, Folder 47)
- East Natural, Soho Natural, Abbigail 867A's Decisions (Box 6, Folder 48)
- ILA Disclaimer for East Natural (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Stores w/ ILA Contracts (Box 6, Folder 50)
- UFCW Locals (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Lawsuit (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Evidence (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Press Release (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Advertisement (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Directions (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Jack's World (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Jack's World (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Greengrocer (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Prints (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Korean Press Translations (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Alpine - Feces Event, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  April 6
- Korean Cless - Clippings (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Green Grocery Campaign (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Adinah's Farms Market (Box 8, Folder 1)
- All American Tanning (Box 8, Folder 2)
- All Bases Covered (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Alliance Leather Corp. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Alling & Cory (Box 8, Folder 5)
- All State Diversified Products (Box 8, Folder 6)
- American Food and Vending Corp. (Box 8, Folder 7)
- American Packaging Corp. (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Atlas Health Care Linen Services (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Au Bon Pain Inc. (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Alfred Dunner Inc. (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Avirex LTD. (Box 8, Folder 12)
- American Presort Co. (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Amish Manhattan Farmers Market (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Ames Linen Service (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Amvent Inc. (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Andel Jewelry Corp. (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Andre Style Fashion (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Androme Leather Inc. (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Angelic Textile Services Inc. (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Apex Leather Corp. (Box 8, Folder 21)
- M. Aron Group (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Art Station LTD (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Art Store (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Arthur Brown & Co. (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Awareness Communications Bookstore (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Azteca Enterprises, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Babbitt Bearings (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Baldwin-Richardson Foods (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Barnes & Noble College Bookstores Inc. (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Barnes & Noble Bookstores (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Belle Knitting Mills (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Berry Company Rochester Phonebook (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Bookstore Organizing Committee (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Center for the Disabled (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Cibao Meat Products Inc. (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Bookstore Organizing Committee - Columbia Barnes & Noble (Box 8, Folder 37)
- BSOC - Columbia Barnes & Noble (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Borders Books (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Bramco Industries Corp. (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Brown Coach (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Cantar Corp. (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Certech Inc. (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Dean Foods Birdseye (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Deli on Madison 420 Gourmet Corp. (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Demi Leather Corp. (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Labyrinth Book Store (Box 9, Folder 1)
- JMB Linen Incorporated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- J's Delicatessen Triple J Inc. (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Jack's 99 cent Store Corp. (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Joe DiMaggio (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Johnstown Leather Corp. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- The Korean Association of New York, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Korean Produce Trucking Corp. (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Kraus & Son Black and Silver Banner (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Denihan, B.J. Inc. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Divine Brothers Inc. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Divine Brothers Customer List (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Dico Customer List (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Divine Brothers Strike, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Divine Brothers Empire (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Fashion Tanning Company Inc. (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Field Staff Union (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Follett Higher Education Group (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Fownes Brothers & Co. Inc. (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Friedman, A.I., LP (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Fuji Apple (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Garden Fruit & Vegetable 420 E. 14th (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Gold & Silver Inc. (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Graceland (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Grandma Browns Beans Inc. (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Grande (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Great Jones Books (Box 9, Folder 27)
- IMP Originals (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Inacom Corp. (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Infants and Juveniles Association (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Interface Solutions ( Formerly Armstrong Industrial Specialties) (Box 9, Folder 31)
- International Controls and Measurement Corp. (Box 9, Folder 32)
- International Food Concepts LTD. (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Hicks and Otts Prints (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Labyrinth Books - Contract Negotiations, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Leathers Best Inc. (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Lectorum Publications Inc. Scholastic Corp. (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Lee's Art Shop Inc. (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Loehmann's Inc. (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Lower Manhattan Alliance For Politcal Action (Box 10, Folder 6)
- M&T Pretzels (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Manhattan Book Co., Inc. Shakespeare & Co. (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Maxam Leather Goods Inc. (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Navarro Special Cleaning (Box 10, Folder 10)
- New York University Medical Center Security Guards (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Northern Health Care Linen Services Inc. (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Notary Info (Box 10, Folder 13)
- North Star Fund (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Nu Way Laundry & Cleaners (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Olympic - Lower East Side Market (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Organic Market (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Orientation Packet Info (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Orion Bus Industries (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Oswego Economic Development News (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Paper & Ink (Box 10, Folder 21)
- People Inc. (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Positive Promotions (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Posman Collegiate Bookstore (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Props for Today Inc. (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Qualimax Cleaners, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Rainbow Linens Inc. (Box 10, Folder 27)
- RCS Rizzoli Corp. (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Robinson & Smith (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Saint Mark's Book Store Inc. (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Salton/Maxim (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Safety - Kleen Systems Inc. (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Sam Flax Inc. (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Pearl Paint Co. Inc. (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Profile Graphics (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Schenectady Int'l Inc. (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Schlegel Corp. (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Schlegel Systems - Products - Copier Components (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Schlegel Systems - Products - EMI (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Schlegel systems - Products - -Weatherstripping (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Schott Brothers Inc. (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Seaboard Atlantic (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Section Eight Inc. (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Simco Leather Corp. (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Shakespeare & Co. (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Soho Art Materials Inc. (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Superb Leather Inc. (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Tartan Textile (Box 10, Folder 48)